https://www.ozaboriginal.com.au/privacy.html

Cushion Covers
16"X16"
Cushion Covers Applique
Cushion Covers Silky 12"X20"
Bessie N Sims
Bridgette Walla..
Camillia Young
Connie King
Donna Hayes
Gordon Young
Iwantja Artist ..
Jane Oliver
Jillary Lynch
Jukurrpa Artist..
Kathleen Wallac..
Keringke Artist..
Kunmanara D Tay..
Pam Hall
Pauline N Galla..
Russell Saunder..
Sharon Williams
Suzie Prince
Terry Johnstone
Tobwabba Artist..
Trish Singer
Walkatjara Arti..
Warlukurlunga A..
Warumpi Artist ..
Whitton Artist ..
About Us
Welcome to OzAboriginal Pty. Ltd.!
OzAboriginal was formed in 1992. Initially located in a warehouse that was primarily used for the distribution of Indigenous products, the organisation began to grow as new skills were learnt and a clear identity was formed. Local Indigenous artists joined the organisation that did traditional painting on artefacts, canvas and giftware. OzAboriginal, provides meaningful employment to local artists whilst allowing them the opportunities to develop their own artistic and commercial profile.
Customer Service
Shipping
Shipping charges are based on the size and weight of the item. You will be shown the shipping and handling charges on the "Purchase Verification" page before you finalize your purchase.
Shop with Confidence
We ensure that the art-work shipped is insured for its full value. The cost of the same is however incorporated in the shipping and handling charges..
Information
Customer Service
About Us
Log In
Create Account
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
General Info
Categories
Discontinued Stock SALEArtefactsCards, Frames, Books, SoapsCoastersBagsFine ArtsJewelleryMetal JewelleryKitchenwareLacquerwareLeather AccessoriesOriginal CuriosRugs and furnishingsScarves, Sarongs & FabricNew Products ...
Artists
Please Select
Alanna Rose
Bessie Liddle
Bessie N Sims
Bridgette Walla..
Camillia Young
Connie King
Donna Hayes
Gordon Young
Iwantja Artist ..
Jane Oliver
Jillary Lynch
Jukurrpa Artist..
Kathleen Wallac..
Keringke Artist..
Kunmanara D Tay..
Lee-Ann Hall
Leslie Kelly
Lisa O'Mara
Marie Oliver
Marie Young
Maringka Burton
Ngarra
Pam Hall
Pauline N Galla..
Russell Saunder..
Sharon Williams
Suzie Prince
Terry Johnstone
Tobwabba Artist..
Trish Singer
Walkatjara Arti..
Warlukurlunga A..
Warumpi Artist ..
Whitton Artist ..
Who's Online
There currently are 12 guests online.
Secure Payments
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in AU privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
If you have opted in for marketing communications, your personal and contact information may be used to receive customised newsletters, offers or updates that may be of interest to the subscriber. Users may opt out to receive future electronic marketing by replying directly to the campaign email.
ozaboriginal.com.au uses cookies to keep track of your personal information such as name, email, address and contact numbers of its online users. Your contact and personal information may reflect during a repeat visit to our website. Analytics data is used by OzAboriginal Pty. Ltd. to generate detailed reports and statistics on website visits.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you toggle cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
As stated above, OzAboriginal website uses cookies and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our website are most popular. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more personalised as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications.
Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data). There are “special categories” of more sensitive personal data which require a higher level of protection. We may collect, store, and use the following categories of personal contact information about you: name, title, addresses, telephone numbers, and email addresses.
Information Disclosure
OzAboriginal Pty. Ltd. will not disclose any information obtained through our website to any third party without the express consent of the individual. OzAboriginal Pty. Ltd. will have a record of the incoming email address if you have sent OzAboriginal Pty. Ltd. an email or submitted an enquiry. We do not provide your email address(es) to mailing lists and we will not send you unsolicited email (SPAM). OzAboriginal will use your email address to respond to your requests and communicate directly with you.
How do we protect visitor information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
Third-party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback concerning these third-party links.
We may use Google Ad Sense Advertising on our website. Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
Changes to this privacy statement
We reserve the right to update this privacy statement at any time, and we will provide you with a new privacy statement when any substantial updates are made. We may also notify you from time to time about the processing of your personal information.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
OzAboriginal Pty. Ltd.
222 Georges River Road
Croydon Park NSW 2133
Australia
Tel: +61 - 2 - 9716 6244
Email : mail@ozaboriginal.com.au
Back
Search
Advanced Search
Important Links
The Australian Indigenous Art Trade Association (Art.Trade)
is the national organisation for persons and organisations experienced in the business of indigenous art, it promotes the ethical trade of indigenous art.
www.arttrade.com.au
The Indigenous Art Code (The Code)
aims to ensure fair trade with Indigenous artists, it promotes fair and transparent dealings within the Industry.
Copyright © 2020 OzAboriginal Pty Ltd..
Developed & Managed by Mind Source.
Site Map
Privacy Notice
